<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-05-06T18:53:58-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">sync.blog</title><subtitle>Official blog for sync.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">The new sync.!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/the-new-sync/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The new sync.!" /><published>2018-05-05T21:40:02-05:00</published><updated>2018-05-05T21:40:02-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/the-new-sync</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/the-new-sync/">&lt;p&gt;As we continue to expand, sync.theater is beginning to adopt a new brand: sync.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will be keeping the same iconic domain name: sync.theater, but going forward we will be adopting the name &lt;span style=&quot;color: #8C5EC1&quot;&gt;sync.&lt;/span&gt; to refer to the app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This new brand consists of a new logo as seen at the top of this blog as well as below, a new set of design principles as well as a more unified color scheme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/imgs/sync%202.svg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With these new changes, users should feel more comfortable navigating the interface of sync. as well as allow us to develop a more recognizable brand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always feel free to give feedback, the links for that can be found on the About page via the link above.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">As we continue to expand, sync.theater is beginning to adopt a new brand: sync. We will be keeping the same iconic domain name: sync.theater, but going forward we will be adopting the name sync. to refer to the app. This new brand consists of a new logo as seen at the top of this blog as well as below, a new set of design principles as well as a more unified color scheme. With these new changes, users should feel more comfortable navigating the interface of sync. as well as allow us to develop a more recognizable brand. As always feel free to give feedback, the links for that can be found on the About page via the link above.</summary></entry></feed>